delawareinc.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy | Harvard Business Services, Inc

Last Modified: May 25, 2018

**Introduction**

Protecting your privacy is important to Harvard Business Services, Inc. (" **Harvard** " or " **we** " or " **us** "). We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Harvard Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website ([www.delawareinc.com](https://www.delawareinc.com/)) (our " **Website** ") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * on this Website
  * in e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Harvard or any third party.
  * any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible on the Website.

Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes or failure to opt out of emails sent to you following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy are deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Minors under the Age of 13**

No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from minors under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features, register on the Website, make any purchases through the Website, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Website or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn that we have collected or received personal information from a minor under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a minor under the age of 13, please contact us at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com).

**What Information Do We Collect About You and How Do We Do It?**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including:  
_Personal Information_

  * Information by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, email address or telephone number, when you correspond with us, call us to make a purchase or request service, or participate in an online survey or chat function.
  * Your social security number or tax identification number if you authorize us to obtain an employment identification number for your new Delaware company.
  * Information you provide when completing your business filing online through the Website.
  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our service or requesting further services.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website.

_Other Information_

  * When you browse Harvard's website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse, not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using.
  * Like many websites, the Harvard website uses cookie technology. When you first connect to our site we identify your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you, except your first name so we can welcome you on your next visit. Cookies help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going and how long they spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site so we can make the site even better.
  * Information about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website, usage details and your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). Please contact us if you wish to opt out of behavioral tracking.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses and information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies.

**Why Do We Collect Personal Information**

Harvard collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service when you form your company and every year thereafter until you close or cancel your company.

As your Delaware Registered Agent, we are required by law to maintain your Contact Person's address. We will use this information to inform you of future Delaware Franchise Tax due dates and offer to fulfill these services for you for a fee. We will inform you of annual Registered Agent fees due. We will send you any service of process packages we may receive as your Registered Agent. If courier fees are necessary to forward service of process, we will charge you a service fee.

It is your responsibility to notify us of any change in address and contact information so we can send you tax compliance notices, Registered Agent invoices and service of process.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including:

  * To fulfill any purpose for which you provide it.
  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  * To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * We may store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests, speed up your searches and recognize you when you return to our Website.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

Communication with Harvard through our website is not intended to create an attorney-client relationship. Harvard Business Services, Inc. is not a law firm, and therefore any information transmitted to Harvard is not considered privileged client-attorney information.

At times, we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your information. We may also disclose information about you if we believe that disclosure is necessary for the public interest.

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of Harvard Business Services, Inc.'s assets, in which personal information held by Harvard Business Services, Inc. about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our [terms of use](https://www.delawareinc.com/terms-of-use/) and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of Harvard Business Services, Inc., our customers or others.

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information.

**_Tracking Technologies and Advertising_**  
You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.

**_Promotional Offers from Harvard_**  
If you do not wish to have your e-mail address and contact information used by Harvard to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt-out by checking the unsubscribe button in our email communications or emailing our support desk at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com).

This opt-out does not apply to information provided to us as a result of a product or service purchase or other transactions.

**_Targeted Advertising_**  
If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our target-audience preferences, you can opt out by emailing us at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com).

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**

We do not give or sell your name, email address, address or any other personal information to any third party for marketing purposes and will reveal such information only if required by law to disclose such information and as otherwise described in this policy.

Every effort to secure your data against criminal outside disclosure is being taken over the internet. Every name and address in our database is initially and periodically checked against the U.S. Treasury Department's SDN list.

We will not sell, rent, lease or share your personal information with any third party without your express permission and as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

Our records are password protected by biometric finger print scanners and monitored by security personnel on site. Your data is monitored by a 16-camera infrared system, backed up by independent propane power supplies, generators and a state of the art, digitally-controlled power management system. Your records are stored in secure facilities with 24-hour surveillance and, in case of a regional disaster, we can start servicing your requests within 48 hours at our location of choice. To learn more about how we protect your information, please ask one of our team members to provide you with a more detailed explanation.

Harvard safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers and make sure you use a secure browser.

Harvard uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To place on-line orders with Harvard, you must use an SSL-enabled browser. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the internet.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

**Accessing and Correcting Your Information**

You can send us an e-mail at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com) to request access to, or to correct or delete, any personal information you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

Proper access and use of information provided on the Website is governed by our [terms of use](https://www.delawareinc.com/terms-of-use/).

**Your California Privacy Right**

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Website that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com).

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Website home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account or through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**Our Companywide Commitment to Privacy**

To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every Harvard employee.

Harvard's website contains links to other sites. Harvard does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

**EU – U.S. Privacy Shield**

Harvard Business Services, Inc. participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU – U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. Harvard is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List. <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>

Harvard is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework. Harvard complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Harvard is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Harvard may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Harvard commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information.  EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should contact us. Harvard has further committed to cooperate with EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.  If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact the EU DPAs for more information or to file a complaint.  The services of EU DPAs are provided at no cost to you.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint> you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

**General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

The GDPR is an EU Regulation to improve the protection of the personal data of EU citizens and increase the obligations of organizations who collect or process personal data. These new regulations take effect on the 25th of May 2018. The regulations greatly enhance the data privacy and security of our customers and extend to them exercisable rights enabling greater control over one's personally identifiable information.

The full specification of the GDPR rights and regulations can be found [here](https://gdpr-info.eu/)

Harvard functions as both a controller and processor of our customers' personally identifiable information (PII). Additionally, we employ a number of sub-processors to which we transmit data for storage or processing beyond feature sets under our immediate control.

As a controller of data, we store PII such as customer names, email addresses, physical addresses, IP addresses, phone numbers and avatars. We use databases through GDPR compliant service providers (MSSQL) to store sensitive customer data.

Harvard is also a processor of customer data. We use customer data to compile legal documents. We have a system-wide GDPR compliance effort underway which will manifest itself on the core Harvard’s website as well as any of our hubs, satellite applications, or other owned properties.

For more information, please see our [GDPR documentation](https://www.delawareinc.com/privacy-policy/gdpr/) or contact [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com) to exercise your personal data access rights.

**This Privacy Policy applies only to your relationship with Harvard.  **It does not apply to the interactions that you have with any other individual, entity, or other group through Harvard’s website. For example, the administrator of an Organization has the ability to disclose or share with other members of the Organization any information that you submit through Harvard’s website.  **Harvard has no control over this disclosure or sharing, and is not responsible for it.  **The protection of your personal data when you interact with an Organization through Harvard is governed solely by any agreements that you may enter into with the Organization and is beyond the scope of this Privacy Policy. 

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you use Harvard’s website, and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect:

• On Harvard’s website;

• In e-mail, text and other electronic messages between you and Harvard, on Harvard website or otherwise; and

• When you interact with our links and applications on third-party websites and services if they include a link to this Privacy Policy.

It does not apply to information collected by:

• Us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Harvard or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or   

• Any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on Harvard’s website.

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use Harvard. By accessing or using Harvard’s website, you agree to this Privacy Policy. 

**What is “personal data”?**  

"Personal data" is any data that (1) is recorded in any form, (2) is about or pertains to a specific individual and (3) can be linked to that individual. For example, and without limitation, your first and last names, address, email address, telephone number, and other contact information, and the deals in which you have participated are "personal data."

**What kind of personal data is collected?**  

We collect personal data at different stages of your use on Harvard’s website.

**When you visit delawareinc.com -  **If you visit delawareinc.com or use an interface which interacts with delawareinc.com, whether or not you sign-in as a registered user, we collect your IP address, the location of your Internet Service Provider, the type and version of Internet browser that you are using, and the website from which you came. We also collect information regarding your site usage, such as the time spent on a page and the number of pages you viewed. 

**When you set up an account -** When you set up your account, you will be required to provide certain personal data including your name and email address. You may also be invited to provide optional personal data, such as biography, photograph, postal address or phone number. If you choose to do so, our use of your personal data shall be governed by this Privacy Policy. 

**When you interact with Harvard’s website -** We also collect personal data that you provide when you interact with Harvard’s website such as, for example, by sending a message or uploading documents, preparing an accelerator application, or when exchanging correspondence with us such as through support emails. 

**When you use your account -** We collect information that you provide or create when you use your account: 

If you provide any information about or personal data of a third party (such as a person's name or photograph), you are representing to Harvard that you have all necessary authority and/or have obtained all necessary consents from such individual to enable Harvard to collect, use and disclose his or her personal data as set forth in this Privacy Policy. If we receive a written complaint or direction from the person, we will take down his or her information and notify you that we have done so. 

**How is personal data collected?**  

We collect personal data directly from you when you provide it through your use of Harvard’s website, such as in emails or when you fill out forms that are displayed on Harvard’s website.

We also use cookies that are sent to your computer, or action tags that are placed on Harvard’s website. For additional explanation on cookies and action tags, see Cookies and Action Tags. 

**For what purpose will my personal data be used?**  

Harvard uses your personal data to maintain your account and fulfill other services offered on Harvard’s website. We also use your personal data to respond to requests that you make of us, and to contact you and to provide you with information that we believe may be of interest to you.

We may also use your name and contact information to make queries to social networking and other sites, such as LinkedIn, for a variety of purposes, including, but not limited to, verifying your identity, and showing you how you are linked or connected to other individuals who are also Harvard users.

Your personal data may also be shared with companies in the Harvard family of companies or to third parties as described below.

**Can third parties see my personal data?**  

No third parties cannot see your personal data.

**With whom may Harvard Business Services share personal data?**  

Under certain business or legal conditions, Harvard may have to disclose your personal data to others as follows:

**• Within the Harvard Family** – Harvard may now or in the future have a parent, subsidiary or related company or companies within the Harvard family of companies. Harvard has the right to share all personal data with all such affiliated companies. 

**• Service Providers**  – Harvard may engage other companies and individuals to perform necessary business functions on behalf of Harvard (e.g. customer service or email provider). If it is necessary to perform these functions, these companies or individuals may have access to personal data of our users. These service providers have agreed not to use the personal data for any other purpose other than providing the required services. 

**• Legally Required Disclosure -** Under certain circumstances, disclosure of your personal data may be required by law. Harvard may disclose your personal data (1) if, in its own best judgment, it is required by law to do so in order to comply with a facially valid judicial or governmental subpoena, warrant, bankruptcy proceedings, or other order, or (2) to a government institution that has asserted its lawful authority to obtain the information, or (3) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud. 

**• Change of Ownership**  \- If ownership of Harvard changes as a result of a merger, acquisition, or transfer to another company, your personal data may be transferred to the successor entity. If such transfer takes place, you will be notified of any material changes to the Privacy Policy and provided with the ability to opt-out of the transfer of your personal data to the successor entity. 

**  Sharing with 3** **rd** **  Parties **

3rd Parties are companies unaffiliated with Harvard.  We may share your personal data with 3rd parties if given permission by you so that they can market their products or services to you. If you do not want us to share your personal data with 3rd parties after giving us permission to do so, contact us at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com)

**Can I access or change my personal data?**  

Upon request Harvard will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If your personal data changes, you may correct, update, or amend by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Mail Department at [mail@delawareinc.com](mailto:mail@delawareinc.com) or by contacting us by postal mail at the contact information listed below.  If you wish to delete/remove/deactivate your profile, remove your testimonial from our site, or opt out of sharing Basic Application Information, please email us at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com). We will respond to your request within 30 days.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active to provide you services.  We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

For auditing and security purposes, Harvard keeps a log of all users' activities, which is retained in its archives as necessary for Harvard to fulfill its obligations. Users may have access to the personal data that pertain to them. In addition, each user's right of access may be limited to the extent that providing access might infringe on a third party's privacy rights. Requests for access to this archived information are handled on a case-by-case basis, after Harvard has verified the identity of the requestor. Inquiries should be made as provided in the section.

**Can I have my personal data deleted?**  

You can delete any personal data that is recorded in the profile that you create for yourself as a client of Harvard’s.

**Social Media Widgets**

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook and Twitter button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

**Testimonials**

We display testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements.  With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name.  If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com). 

**Invite Members**

If you choose to invite a user to our platform, we will ask you for a name and email address.  We will automatically send your invite a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  Harvard stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of invites claimed. Your invitee may contact us at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**What is Website Data, and how is it used?**  

Website data is aggregated data about the overall traffic to, and usage of Harvard’s website. Examples include the number of visitors to the delawareinc.com website and the number of registered users of Harvard’s website. Harvard may extract and use website data for internal purposes, in order to analyze the performance of our website and applications. For example, we may use these data for traffic analysis and business decision making, in order to determine how we can improve our site or its functionalities.

The statistics generated in this manner contain no personal data and cannot be used to gather any information about individual visitors to the site.

**Cookies and other Tracking Technologies**

We and our partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  

**• Cookies  ** 

Harvard uses 'cookies.' A cookie is a small amount of data sent to a user's web browser from a web server, which is then stored on the user's hard drive. Cookies are used to make site navigation easier, and can help recognize a returning visitor. Harvard’s cookies do not generate any personal data, do not read personal data from your computer, and are not tied to any personal data. Most browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies, or to prompt you before accepting cookies from the sites that you visit. If you decide not to accept our cookies, some or all features of the site may not be available because navigation on the site is facilitated by cookies. You can delete cookies from your computer at any time. You can learn more about cookies by visiting: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) or [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/). 

**• Action Tags  ** 

Harvard uses action tags. An action tag is a small piece of code that is placed on a webpage or in an email in order to track the pages viewed or the messages opened, the date and time when someone visited our website, the website from which the visitor came, the type of browser used, and the domain name and address of the user's Internet Service Provider. Action tags allow us to better understand how users and visitors use our site or browse through our pages, so that we can improve access to and navigation through the site, add or modify pages, according to our user's patterns. Action tags cannot be removed or deleted by our users, because they are part of the programming of a webpage.

**• Log Files  ** 

Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you access a web page. When you use Harvard’s website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends out whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.) and URLs, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed, and other similar information.

**• Web Beacons  ** 

When you use Harvard’s website, we may employ web beacons, which are used to track the online usage patterns of Users anonymously. No personal data from your account is collected using these beacons. In addition, we may also use web beacons in HTML-based emails sent to Users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

The use of cookies or similar technologies by our partners is not covered by our privacy policy.  We do not have access or control over these cookies or similar technologies.

**• Behavioral Targeting**  

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) ). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

**• Do Not Track Signals  ** 

Harvard does not track or use Do Not Track signals.  

**What security measures are in place to protect my personal data?**  

Harvard uses physical, technical, and administrative procedures in order to safeguard and protect personal data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. However, while we do our best to implement reasonable security measures, we do not guarantee that our safeguards will always work.

Harvard uses industry-standard technological means to protect your personal data while in transit through the Internet. We use encryption and a comprehensive authentication protocol to provide reasonable security. However, please remember that no security system on the Internet is perfect.  If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [techsupport@delawareinc.com](mailto:techsupport@delawareinc.com).

**What about Uploaded Documents?**  

Documents that are uploaded to your client portal for sharing are stored at a third party data-storage service. All uploads and downloads are transmitted through the web between users and the data storage service using the same encryption techniques as those that are used with personal data. However, uploaded documents are neither stored redundantly, nor backed up. Therefore, we recommend that Harvard users keep back-up copies of their documents if they upload them to the delawareinc.com website.

**When will Harvard contact me?**  

Harvard will communicate with you in response to your requests for service or customer support. We will contact you by phone or by email, according to your preference.

Harvard will contact you when we receive Service of Process or any communications from the state of Delaware or any other state where we have filed documents on your behalf.

Harvard will send you weekly or monthly invitations to read our blog and our latest blog articles.

Harvard will send you service-related emails if it becomes necessary to do so. Harvard may send you an email in order to notify you of updates to our Privacy Policy, Terms of Service, or other agreement that you have with Harvard. Harvard may also send you an email in order to notify you of new products, or services or features. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, you may opt out of them by clicking on the unsubscribe button. For system generated emails (in response to you or other Harvard users actions) the majority of them are configurable under settings.

If you do not want to receive any emails from Harvard, you can opt out by deactivating your account by contacting [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com)

**Links to other websites**  

Harvard may provide links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these sites. In order to safeguard your privacy, please review the privacy policies of any sites that you may visit before providing any personal data to these third party sites.

**Limitation of Liability**  

Harvard exercises reasonable efforts to safeguard the security and confidentiality of your personal data; however, transmissions protected by industry standard technology and administered by humans cannot be guaranteed to be secure. Harvard will not be liable for unauthorized disclosure of personal data that occurs through no fault of Harvard including, but not limited to, errors in transmission, access to your account by anyone uses your user ID and password, your failure to comply with your security obligations, and the unauthorized acts of Harvard's employees.

**Choice**  

If at any time Harvard wishes to disclose, or use your personal data in a way, or for a purpose other than as described in this Privacy Policy, Harvard will give you the opportunity to choose (opt out) whether your personal data (1) may be disclosed to a third party and (2) may be used for a purpose other than the purposes that are set forth in this Privacy Policy.  If you do not want us to share your personal data with these members, contact us at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com)

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  

From time to time, Harvard may update this Privacy Policy in order to reflect changes in its practices. Whenever such changes are made, Harvard will post an updated Privacy Policy on its website and may email registered users. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

All changes will apply to the personal data that are already collected, and to personal data that are collected after the effective date of the revised Privacy Policy, and will become effective when posted.

You will have the right to terminate your account at any time.

**Contacting Harvard Business Services, Inc.**

Harvard Business Services, Inc. owns and operates the delawareinc.com web site. Our mailing address is 16192 Coastal Hwy. Lewes, DE 19958 USA.

**Contact Information**

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 1-302-645-7400 or via email at [privacy@delawareinc.com](mailto:privacy@delawareinc.com).
